Caryn Feist

PROFILE

Executive Chef with experience overseeing multiple upscale, full-service restaurants. Eleven years of progressive responsibility in food preparation, menu development, and management of back-of-the-house operations. People oriented manager who is passionate about food, quality, and customer service, as well as motivating and mentoring team members.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Executive Chef

Lamberti's Cucina, San Diego, CA | March 2015 — Present

- Create menus and standards leading to exemplary dining experiences across four local dining establishments
- Lead and train culinary teams and ensure training material and processes enable delivery of exceptional dining experiences in all locations
- Collaborate with chef partners across the enterprise
- Liaise with supply chain management to identify potential supplier relationships
- Address quality and/or service gaps
- Develop food service equipment plans to meet budgetary goals

Sous Chef

Jenny's House, N. Hollywood, CA | January 2009 — February 2015

- Supervised food preparation and presentation to ensure quality and restaurant standards
- Worked with executive chef to maintain kitchen organization and staff ability
- Led kitchen staff when chef was unavailable
- Oversaw and organized kitchen stock and ingredients
- Kept cooking stations stocked prior to prime operation hours
- Managed food and product ordering
- Hired and trained new kitchen employees
- Minimized waste and managed budgetary concerns

CERTIFICATIONS

 CCC Certified Chef de Cuisine, American Culinary Federation (ACF) | 2018

EDUCATION

Master Chef Certificate Program

Chef Eric's Culinary Classroom, Los Angeles, CA 90064 October 2009 — February 2009

Associate of Science in Culinary Arts

Art Institute Of California, N. Hollywood, CA September 2016 — March 2018

KEY SKILLS

- Highly developed culinary expertise
- Seasonal menu development
- Knowledge of a variety of ethnic/regional cuisines
- Development of special event menus
- Standardizing recipes to ensure consistent quality in preparation and presentation
- Strong personal work ethic
- Guest driven focus on quality, service, and overall dining experience
- Administer budget for costs of food, beverage, and labor
- Sound knowledge of FDA and major U.S. metropolitan city health code adherence
- Leadership in full-service restaurant environments
- Ability to anticipate problems and create innovative solutions
- Excellent communication skills and computer proficiency
- Ability to manage multiple projects under tight deadlines